# Rahul Kumar Jhamtani

rahulkumarjhamtani@gmail.com | (+91)-72209-88840 <u>rahulkumarjhamtani.github.io</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/rahuljhamtani</u>

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### WEB DESIGNER AND PRESENTER

Vedik Cyber Forces (VCF)
August 2020 to Present
Lead in the design, development and implementation of the graphic, layout, production and communication.

#### **WEB DESIGNER**

Tribal Connect: Connecting Our Roots

June 2021 - September 2021

Intern as a Web Designer and feeling great to work
for an NGO. Made gallery for them which contains
multiple images of their events.

#### WEB DESIGNER AND DEVELOPER

The Sparks Foundation

August 2021 - September 2021

I had completed both the tasks of web development (Basic Banking System, Payment Gateway Integration).

## EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

#### **Anand International College of Engineering**

Jaipur, Raj.

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2019 - Present

Anand-ICE, one of the finest private engineering colleges in Jaipur, has probably the best brains as teachers and scientists to facilitate premium academic excellence along with the nuances of ethics and human values.

#### Maheshwari Public School

Jaipur, Raj.
Primary and Secondary Schooling
2007-2019

Affiliated to the Central Board of Senior Secondary Education, it prepares students for 10+2 pattern of examination catering to Science and Commerce faculties.

## **SUMMARY**

I'm a 21 year old web designer and developer with a focus on new technology, content, and layout design. I want to work across the full stack of Software Development. I've built a few projects by myself and I'm looking for a role where I can grow and learn from other experienced team members and my friends.

# SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS and JS
- SQL
- C/C++
- Communication

# **HACKATHONS**

#### SoftTech Hack-2021(Offline and Online)

Anand ICE 9th & 10th March 2021 Won 1st Prize

# SITE-2K21 (Offline)

Shankara Institute Of Technology 19th & 20th March 2021 Participation

# HOBBIES

- Playing cricket
- Watching movies
- Listening to music
- Dance
- Communicating with others